Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- News Clippings, 1961-1996; Series V; 1.68; (5 boxes)
  - Undated Articles (Box 27, Folder 516)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 960
  - Undated Articles (Box 27a, Folder 516a)
  - UFW Collected Clipping Sheets, 1975-76, n.d.
- California Labor Relations Act Collection, 1968-1994; Series VI; 1.26; (3 boxes)
  Series VI, California Labor Relations Act Collection, is organized into two subseries: Audiotapes and Written Collection. The audiotapes are arranged in roughly chronological order, and are restricted; reference copies have been made on CD-ROM. The Written Collection is organized into Agricultural Bills, General Materials, Initiatives, JEL Research 1975, Post Law, Tape Transcripts, Post 1988 Material, and Press Clippings.
  - AUDIOTAPES
    Box 65 contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - CALRA Tape 1. Jerry Cohen and UFW attorneys Sandy Nathan and Tony Gaenslen, 1975 June 19; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885554)
      Transcript: Volume 39 Historical Record (HR): 1-125, stored in: box 29, folder 571
    - CALRA Tape 2. Jerry Cohen and UFW attorneys Sandy Nathan and Tony Gaenslen, 1975 June 19; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885562)
    - CALRA Tape 3. Cesar Chavez on 1,000-mile march from Soledad to Gonzalez, 1975 August 1; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885570)
      Transcript: File 40 CC: 1-7, stored in: box 29, folder 572
    - CALRA Tape 4. Senate Industrial Labor Relations Committee hearing in Sacramento, Assembly Labor Relations Committee hearing, 1975 May 7-12; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885588)
    - CALRA Tape 5. Assembly Labor Relations Committee hearing continued. Governor Brown signing CALRA bill and press conference, 1975 May 12-June 5; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885596)
    - CALRA Tape 6. LeRoy Chatfield in Sacramento, 1975 May 12; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885604)
      Transcript: File 41: 1-15, stored in: box 29, folder 573
    - CALRA Tape 7. Cesar Chavez in Berkeley. Alan Grant at Farm Bureau on Phone, 1975 May 15-17; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885612)
      Transcript: File 42: 1-5; File 43: 1-38, stored in: box 29, folders 574-575
    - CALRA Tape 8. Governor Brown press conference and interview, 1975 May 19-20; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885620)
      Transcript: File 44: 1-13, stored in: box 29, folder 576
    - CALRA Tape 9. Senate Finance Committee hearing, Debate on State Senate floor, 1975 May 20-26; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885638)
    - CALRA Tape 10. Assembly floor debate, 1975 May 29; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885646)
    - CALRA Tape 11. Cesar Chavez press conferences in Livingstone during Gallo voting and in Napa, 1975 September 10-14; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885653)
    - CALRA Tape 12. Sandy Nathan on implementation of CALRA in Salinas area, 1975 September 24; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885661)
      Transcript: Volume 45: 41-60, stored in: box 29, folder 577
    - CALRA Tape 13: Cesar Chavez from San Francisco to Livermore on elections, etc., 1975 September 25; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885679)
      Transcript: Volume 45: 38-40, stored in: box 29, folder 577
    - CALRA Tape 14: Ellen Greenstone in Salinas on implementation of law, Jerry Goldman, 1975 September 25; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885687)
      Transcript: Volume 45: 8-25, stored in: box 29, folder 577
    - CALRA Tape 15: Jerry Goldman in Salinas continued, 1975 September 25; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885695)
      Transcript: Volume 45: 25-38, stored in: box 29, folder 577
    - CALRA Tape 16: Sam Cohen in Sacramento, John Rice Trujillo, 1975 October 30; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885703)
    - CALRA Tape 17: John Rice Trujillo in Sacramento continued, 1975 October 30; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104885711)
  - WRITTEN COLLECTION
    - Agricultural Bills
      - File 1 CALRA: NLRA, 1968
      - File 2 CALRA: Cory Bill, 1971, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 534)
      - File 3 CALRA: SB 40, 1971 Sep 23 (Box 28, Folder 535)
      - File 4 CALRA: AB 3370, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 536)
      - File 5 CALRA: AB 1, 1975, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 537)
      - File 6 CALRA: Brown Bill (SB 813), 1975, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 538)
      - File 7 CALRA: SB 1 (special session), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 539)
      - File 8 CALRA: Other 1975 Ag Bills (Box 28, Folder 540)
      - File 9 CALRA: Ag Labor Bill Comparisons, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 541)
      - File 10 CALRA: Assembly Labor Relations Hearing, 1976 Mar 15 (Box 28, Folder 542)
    - General Material
      - File 11 CALRA: Assembly Labor Relations Hearing, 1975 May 12 (Box 28, Folder 543)
      - File 12 CALRA: Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 544)
      - File 13 CALRA: Events of May 19, 1975, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 545)
      - File 14 CALRA: Special Session, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 546)
      - File 15 CALRA: UFW Internal Memos, 1975 May 19 (Box 28, Folder 547)
      - File 16 CALRA: UFW Press Releases, 1975-76 (Box 28, Folder 548)
      - File 17 CALRA: Union Discipline (Box 28, Folder 549)
    - Initiatives
      - File 18 CALRA: Prop. 22, 1972, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 550)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 966
      - File 19 CALRA: Prop. 14, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 551)
    - Jacques Levy Research, '75-'76
      - File 20 CALRA: Bishops' Committee, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 552)
      - File 21 CALRA: 1975 Notes, [1975], n.d. (Box 28, Folder 553)
      - File 22 CALRA: Rennick J. Harris, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 554)
    - Post Law
      - File 23: Complaints about CALRA, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 555)
      - File 24: CALRB Comments on Regulations, 1975, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 556)
      - File 25: CALRB Internal Memos, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 557)
      - File 26: CALRB Petition Cases, 1975, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 558)
      - File 27: CALRB Press Releases, 1975-76 (Box 29, Folder 559)
      - File 28: CALRB Regulations & Forms, 1975, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 560)
      - File 29: Elections Analysis, 1976 Jan (Box 29, Folder 561)
      - File 30: Elections Results: CALRB, 1975-76 (Box 29, Folder 562)
      - File 31: Election Results: UFW, 1975-76 (Box 29, Folder 563)
      - File 32: Gallo Election, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 564)
      - File 33: Gallo Literature, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 565)
      - File 34: Prop. 14 Chronology, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 566)
      - File 35: Teamster Literature, 1975, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 567)
        Stored also in: Oversize, box 51, folder 967
      - File 36: UFW Elections Literature, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 568)
      - File 37: UFW First Contracts, 1976 Jan 21 (Box 29, Folder 569)
      - File 38: UFW vs. West Foods, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 570)
    - Tape Transcripts
      - File 39: Historical Record (HR), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 571)
      - File 40: Cesar Chavez on 1,000 Mile March, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 572)
      - File 41: LeRoy Chatfield, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 573)
      - File 42: Allan Grant, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 574)
      - File 43: CC Interview, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 575)
      - File 44: Gov. Brown Interview, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 576)
      - File 45: Law's Execution, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 577)
        Includes as part of transcript Levy's written notes from Jerry Cohen, Marshall Ganz, Cesar Chavez's complaints
    - Post 1988 Material
      - File 46: CALRB Annual Report '88-'89, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 578)
      - File 47: UC Article on ALRB, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 579)
      - File 48: CALRB Annual Report '91-'92, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 580)
      - File 49: CALRB Official Notice, 1992 Dec (Box 29, Folder 581)
      - File 50: Mario Saikhon Case Decision, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 582)
      - File 51: UFW Victories Delayed for Years, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 583)
      - File 52: CALRB Handbook, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 584)
      - File 53: Scheid Makewhole Award, 1994, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 585)
      - File 54: ALRB Approves $1.6M Settlement, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 586)
      - File 55: Dolores Huerta Testimony, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 587)
      - File 56: CALRB Hearing Materials, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 588)
      - File 57: Ace Makewhole Award, 1994 Jun 14 (Box 30, Folder 589)
      - File 58: CALRB Election Results '75-'94, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 590)
      - File 59: ALRB Decline, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 591)
    - Press Clippings
      - File 60: Press Clips, 1969-75, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 592)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 968
      - File 61: Press Clips, 1975 Apr-May, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 593)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 969
      - File 62: Press Clips, 1975 May, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 594)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 970
      - File 63: Press Clips, 1975-76, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 595)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 971
      - File 64: Additional Press Clippings, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 596-598)
        Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 972
- Post Mortem Research, 1981-1997; Series VII; 4.40; (15 boxes)
  Series VII, Post Mortem Research, is organized into two subseries: Audiotapes and Written Collection. The Written Collection is further organized into General Files, Oversized Files, and FBI. The subject files in the General File are arranged in alphabetical order. The audiotapes are restricted; reference copies on CD-ROM have been made.
  - AUDIOTAPES
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - PMR Last Days Tape 1: Helen Chavez, Richard Chavez, Dolores Huerta, Marcos Camacho, David Martinez, Paul Chavez, Anthony Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Anna Chavez, Arturo Rodriguez, David Villarino, 1993 November 27-28; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885786)
      Transcript: Volume 1 Last Days: 1-88, Volume 6 MY: 1-20, stored in: box 31, folder 672, 680
    - PMR Last Days Tape 2: Helen Chavez, Richard Chavez, Dolores Huerta, Marcos Camacho, David Martinez, Paul Chavez, Anthony Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Anna Chavez, Arturo Rodriguez, David Villarino, 1993 November 27-28; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885794)
    - PMR Last Days Tape 3: Helen Chavez, Richard Chavez, Dolores Huerta, Marcos Camacho, David Martinez, Paul Chavez, Anthony Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Anna Chavez, Arturo Rodriguez, David Villarino, 1993 November 27-28; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885802)
    - PMR Last Days Tape 4: Mike Ybarra continued, 1993 November 28; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885810)
      Transcript: Volume 6, MY: 20-34, stored in: box 31, folder 680
    - PMR [Marcos] Camacho & [Irv] Herschenbaum Tape 1: La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885828)
      Transcript: Volume 5 C&H: 1-40, stored in: box 31, folder 679
    - PMR [Marcos] Camacho & [Irv] Herschenbaum Tape 2: La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885836)
    - PMR Mike Ybarra in SR Tape 1, 1994 January 14; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885844)
      Transcript: Volume 6 MY: 35-155, stored in: box 31, folder 680
    - PMR Mike Ybarra in SR Tape 2, 1994 January 13; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885851)
    - PMR Mike Ybarra in SR Tape 3, 1994 January 14; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885869)
    - PMR Mike Ybarra in SR Tape 4, 1994 January 14; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885877)
    - PMR Family Tape 1: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 18; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885885)
      Transcript: Volume 2 Family: 1-299, stored in: box 31, folders 674-676
    - PMR Family Tape 2: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 18; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885893)
    - PMR Family Tape 3: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 18; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885901)
      Transcript: Volume 2 Family: 1-299, stored in: box 31, folders 674-676 Transcript
    - PMR Family Tape 4: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 18; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885919)
    - PMR Family Tape 5: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 19; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885927)
    - PMR Family Tape 6: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 19; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885935)
    - PMR Family Tape 7: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 19; 1 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104885943)
    - PMR Family Tape 8: Helen Chavez, Paul Chavez, Richard Chavez, Linda Chavez Rodriguez, Elizabeth Chavez Villarino, Eloise Chavez Carillo, 1994 February 19; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887295)
    - PMR Helen Chavez Tape 1: Helen Chavez, La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887303)
      Transcript: Volume 3 HC: 1-14, stored in box 31, folder 677
    - PMR RC Tape 1: Richard Chavez, La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887329)
      Transcript: Volume 3 RC: 1-101, stored in: box 31, folder 677
    - PMR RC Tape 2: Richard Chavez, La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887337)
    - PMR RC Tape 3: Richard Chavez, La Paz, 1994 June 14; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887311)
    - PMR FC Tape 1: Fernando Chavez, Polly at his home, 1994 March 24; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887345)
      Transcript: Volume 4 FC: 1-42, stored in: box 31, folder 678
    - PMR FC Tape 2: Fernando Chavez, Polly, 1994 March 28; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887352)
    - PMR SC Tape 1: Sylvia Chavez at Polly's house, 1994 March 28; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887360)
      Transcript: Volume 4 SC: 1-39, stored in: box 31, folder 678
    - PMR JC Tape 1: Jerry Cohen, 1993 September 20; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887378)
      Transcript: Volume 8 JC: 1-181, stored in box 32, folders 683-684
    - PMR JC Tape 2: Jerry Cohen, 1993 September 20; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887386)
    - PMR JC Tape 3: Jerry Cohen, 1993 September 20; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887394)
    - PMR JC Tape 4: Jerry Cohen, 1993 September 21; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887402)
    - PMR JC Tape 5: Jerry Cohen in car to Delano, 1993 October 15; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887410)
      Transcript: Volume 8 JC: 182-270, stored in: box 32, folder 683-684
    - PMR JC Tape 6: Jerry Cohen in car, 1993 October 15; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887428)
    - PMR MG Tape 1: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887436)
      Transcript: Volume 9 MG: 1-266, stored in: box 32, folders 685-687 Cassette 6 side B is blank after the set up
    - PMR MG Tape 2: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887444)
    - PMR MG Tape 3: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104887451)
    - PMR MG Tape 4: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887469)
    - PMR MG Tape 5: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 8-9; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887477)
    - PMR MG Tape 6: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 9; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887485)
    - PMR MG Tape 7: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 9; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887493)
    - PMR MG Tape 8: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 9; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887501)
    - PMR MG Tape 9: Marshall Ganz in Cambridge, 1994 April 9; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887519)
    - PMR JD Tape 1: James "Jim" Drake - Bronx, NY, 1993 December 18; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887527)
      Transcript: Volume 11 JD: 1-32, stored in: box 33, folder 689
    - PMR JD Tape 2: James "Jim" Drake - Bronx, NY, 1993 December 18; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887535)
    - PMR FR Jr. Tape 1: Fred Ross, Jr. in Berkeley, 1993 November 23; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887543)
      Transcript: Volume 11 FR Jr.: 1-57, stored in: box 33, folder 689
    - PMR FR Jr. Tape 2: Fred Ross, Jr. in Berkeley, 1993 November 23; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887550)
    - PMR FR Jr. Tape 3: Fred Ross, Jr. in Berkeley, 1993 November 23; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887568)
    - PMR LC Tape 1: LeRoy Chatfield at Loaves and Fishes, 1994 February 10; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887576)
      Transcript: Volume 10 LC: 1-39, stored in: box 31, folder 688
    - PMR LC Tape 2: LeRoy Chatfield at Loaves and Fishes, Sacramento, 1994 February 10; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887584)
    - PMR CH Tape 1: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 March 17; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887592)
      Transcript: Volume 7 CH: 1-25, stored in: box 32, folders 681-682
    - PMR CH Tape 2: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 April 22; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887600)
      Transcript: Volume 7 CH: 26-74, stored in: box 32, folders 681-682
    - PMR CH Tape 3: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 April 22; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887618)
    - PMR CH Tape 4: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 May 5; 1 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104887626)
      Transcript: Volume 7 CH: 75-115, stored in: box 32, folders 681-682
    - PMR CH Tape 5: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 May 5; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887634)
    - PMR CH Tape 6: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 May 19; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887642)
      Transcript: Volume 7 CH: 116-167, stored in: box 32, folders 681-682.
    - PMR CH Tape 7: Chris Hartmire - Sacramento, 1994 May 19; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887659)
    - PMR JB Tape 1: Jerry Brown at his house, 1994 December 18; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887667)
      Transcript: Volume 12 JB: 1-47, stored in: box 33, folders 690-691
    - PMR JB Tape 2: Jerry Brown at his house, 1994 December 18; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887675)
    - PMR JB Tape 3: Jerry Brown at his San Francisco home, 1995 January 14; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887683)
      Transcript: Volume 12 JB: 48-115, stored in: box 33, folders 690-691
    - PMR JB Tape 4: Jerry Brown at his San Francisco home, 1995 January 14; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887691)
    - PMR JB Tape 5: Jerry Brown at his home, 1995 January 21; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887709)
      Transcript: Volume 12 JB: 116-150, stored in: box 33, folders 690-691
    - PMR JB Tape 6: Jerry Brown at "We the People" in Oakland, 1995 March 4; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887717)
      Transcript: Volume 12 JB: 151-219, stored in: box 33, folders 690-691
    - PMR JB Tape 7: Jerry Brown at "We the People" in Oakland, 1995 March 4; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887725)
    - PMR JB Tape 8: Jerry Brown in Oakland, 1995 April 8; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887733)
      Transcript: Volume 12 JB: 220-252, stored in: box 33, folders 690-691
    - PMR GH Tape 1: George Higgins - Washington, 1994 April 11; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887741)
      Transcript: File 52 GH: 1-26, stored in box 37, folder 743
    - PMR Dr. JL Tape 1: Dr. Jerome Lackner - Sacramento, 1994 March 17; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887758)
      Transcript: File 35 Dr. JL: 1-16, stored in: box 36, folder 726
    - PMR DM Tape 1: David Martinez at Stanford, 1994 March 3; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887766)
      Transcript: Volume 15 DM: 1-27, stored in: box 33, folders 694-695
    - PMR EE Tape 1: Ellen Eggers, 1994 June 2; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887774)
      Transcript: Volume 14 EE: 1-91, stored in: box 33, folder 693
    - PMR EE Tape 2: Ellen Eggers, 1994 June 2; 1 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104887782)
    - PMR KB Tape 1: Kit Bricca, 1994 February 1; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887808)
      Transcript: File 27 KB: 1-32, stored in: box 36, folder 718
    - PMR DK Tape 1: Daniel Kingman at his Sacramento home and Phil S. / March rally in Sacramento, J. Brown speaking, 1994 April 24; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887816)
      Transcript: File 34 DK: 1-9, stored in: box 38, folder 748
    - PMR DK Tape 2: Cesar Chavez: Gran Hombre de la Tierra by Kingman, rehearsal of Kingman's composition by the Camillia Symphony Orchestra, undated; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887824)
    - PMR RTH Tape 1: Roy T. Harris, 1993 September 27; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887832)
    - PMR FA Tape 1: Fred Abad at Delano / Jerry Cohen in car, 1993 October 15; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887840)
    - PRM EE Tape 3: Ellen Eggers, 1994 June 2; 1 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104887790)
  - WRITTEN COLLECTION
    - General Files
      - Vol. 1. Last Days, Delano, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 672-673)
        Includes a typescript, corrected plan for Chapter 1
      - Vol. 2. Family at La Paz, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 674-676)
      - Vol. 3. Family: Richard C. and Helen C. at La Paz (Box 31, Folder 677)
      - Vol. 4. Family: Fernando C., Sylvia C. Delgado (Box 31, Folder 678)
      - Vol. 5. Camacho and Hershenbaum, 1994 Jun (Box 31, Folder 679)
      - Vol. 6. Mike Ybarra, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 680)
      - Vol. 7. Wayne C. (Chris) Hartmire, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 681-682)
      - Vol. 8. Jerry Cohen, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 683-684)
      - Vol. 9. Marshall Ganz, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 685-687)
      - Vol. 10. LeRoy Chatfield, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 688)
      - Vol. 11. Fred Ross Jr., Jim Drake, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 689)
      - Vol. 12. Governor Jerry Brown, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 690-691)
      - Vol. 13. Governor Jerry Brown questions, and collected tags, 1995, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 692)
        Includes a clipping: an interview with Jerry Brown dated January 8, 1995
      - Vol. 14. Ellen Eggers, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 693)
      - Vol. 15. David Martinez, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 694-695)
      - Vol. 16. Letters: Cesar Chavez and Fred Ross (Box 34, Folder 696)
        For reference use only. May not be reproduced
      - Vol. 17. Cesar Chavez UCSB Lecture 1 and 5/2 Speech by Cecilia Ruiz (Box 34, Folder 697)
      - Vol. 18. Cesar Chavez UCSB 1992 Core Material for Lectures, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 698-700)
      - Vol. 19. Cesar Chavez Foundation Contracts and Negotiations (Box 34, Folder 701-702)
      - Vol. 20. CALRA Interview 1975, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 703)
      - Vol. 21. CALRA '75 Interview and JC Combined (Box 35, Folder 704-707)
      - Vol. 22. CALRA Collected Division Tags, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 708-709)
      - Vol. 23. CALRA Collected Scene Tags, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 710-711)
      - Vol. 24. CALRA Collected Scene Tags, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 712-714)
      - Vol. 25. CALRA Collected Subject Tags, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 715-716)
      - File 26. Bishops' Committee, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 717)
      - File 27. Kit Bricca, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 718)
      - File 28. Jerry Brown JEL Letter, 1995 Apr 14 (Box 36, Folder 719)
      - File 29. Questions for Jerry Brown, 1994-95 (Box 36, Folder 720)
      - File 30. Kathleen Brown's Speech, 1994 Jan (Box 36, Folder 721)
      - File 31. CALRA Tag Index, 1995, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 722)
      - File 32. Cardinal Roger Mahony Homily, [1993] (Box 36, Folder 723)
      - File 33. Catalogue of News Clippings, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 724)
      - File 34. Chavez Family/JEL Correspondence, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 725)
      - File 35. Cesar Chavez Foundation Negotiations, [1993]-96, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 726)
      - File 36. Cesar Chavez Interview for JFK Library, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 727)
      - File 37. Cesar Chavez Legacy, 1993 Nov 30 (Box 37, Folder 728)
      - File 38. Cesar Chavez Memorial, 1993 Apr 25 (Box 37, Folder 729)